<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<resources>

    <string name="help_wallet">
<![CDATA[
		<p>
			The upper left part of the screen displays your balance in Bitcoins and one selected national currency.
			Tap to go to the list of national currencies, and tap on one of the currencies to select it as default.
		</p>
		<p>
			The QR code on the right contains your bitcoin address and can be used for scanning by another party.
			Tap on the QR code to get a larger version of it.
		</p>
		<p>
			The bottom of the screen is covered by your transactions list, which is empty at the beginning.
			Pending transactions are greyed out until they are confirmed.
			Tap on one entry to add the senders or receivers address to the address book.
		</p>
		<p>
			You can send or request coins by tapping the buttons in the action bar.
			More options are available in the options menu.
		</p>
	]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_request_coins">
<![CDATA[
		<p>
			Using this dialog, you can request coins from another person (who should already have installed Bitcoin Wallet).
		</p>
		<p>
			First, you can enter an amount of Bitcoins to request.
		</p>
		<p>
			Then, you either have the generated QR code scanned by the other person.
			Or, you can send your request to a remote person with the share button in the action bar.
			The other person will have to click the Bitcoin URL.
		</p>
		<p>
			Either way, the other person will be presented a dialog for sending coins with all fields pre-populated.
			If she accepts, all she needs to do is sending the payment.
		</p>
	]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_send_coins">
<![CDATA[
		<p>
			You have initiated the process of sending coins.
			You came here either through the main screen or by clicking on a Bitcoin URL in your mobile browser.
		</p>
		<p>
			First, you enter the Bitcoin address to pay to.
			The address will autocomplete from known entries in your address book.
			You can also scan QR codes with Bitcoin addresses or Bitcoin requests by pressing the QR button in the action bar.
		</p>
		<p>
			Next, you can see how many Bitcoins you can spend at the moment.
			Any difference to the balance from the main screen is still unconfirmed and can thus not yet be spent.
		</p>
		<p>
			Last, you enter the amount to pay.
		</p>
		<p>
			You can enter a payment while being offline.
			It will be sent on next restart of Bitcoin Wallet.
			If you want a payment to be processed as fast as possible, make sure you are well connected (i.e. on a WLAN).
		</p>
		<p>
			Note:
			Payments are irreversible!
			Always check the receiving address.
		</p>
	]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_safety">
<![CDATA[
		<p>
			<b>Important safety notes:</b>
		</p>
		<p>
			Bitcoins are stored on the device.
			<b>If you lose it, you\'ll lose your Bitcoins.</b>
		</p>
		<p>
			This means you need to <b>back up your wallet</b>!
			Use the in-app backup facility for this, rather than a third party backup app.
			Keep your backup safe and remember the password.
		</p>
		<p>
			<b>Before uninstalling</b> (or clearing app data/wiping your device), <b>transfer your Bitcoins to another wallet</b>.
			Remaining Bitcoins will be lost.
		</p>
		<p>
			<b>Payments are irreversible</b>.
			If you send your Bitcoins into the void, there is almost no way to get them back.
		</p>
		<p>
			<b>Keep your mobile device safe!</b>
			Do not root your device.
			Do only install apps you fully trust.
			Malicious apps could be trying to steal your wallet.
		</p>
		<p>
			Keep the risk low!
			<b>Only use with small amounts</b> for day use.
		</p>
	]]>
    </string>

</resources>